{
    "subject": "resource/Another_48_Hrs.",
    "predicate": "ontology/starring",
    "object": "resource/Eddie_Murphy",
    "human_readable": "Eddie Murphy stars in Another 48 Hrs.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.6753827929496765,
            "question": "What movie stars Eddie Murphy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6040849089622498,
            "question": "Who is the main actor in Another 48 Hrs.?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.502221405506134,
            "question": "Has Eddie Murphy acted in other buddy cop movies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46961265802383423,
            "question": "Are there any sequels to Another 48 Hrs.?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42836228013038635,
            "question": "Who directed Another 48 Hrs.?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39927545189857483,
            "question": "What year was Another 48 Hrs. released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38645875453948975,
            "question": "Were there any memorable scenes or lines from Another 48 Hrs.?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36735039949417114,
            "question": "What genre is Another 48 Hrs. likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35771259665489197,
            "question": "Is Eddie Murphy known for action movies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30717864632606506,
            "question": "What was the critical reception of Another 48 Hrs.?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Eddie Murphy stars in Another 48 Hrs.",
            "html": "dbpedia_462_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Eddie Murphy known for action movies?",
            "html": "dbpedia_462_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is Another 48 Hrs. likely to be?",
            "html": "dbpedia_462_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any memorable scenes or lines from Another 48 Hrs.?",
            "html": "dbpedia_462_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_462_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_462_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_462_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_462_134.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_462_149.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_462_167.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_462_169.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_462_181.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_462_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_462_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I found that:\n\n* The document with file path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_462/re-ranker-msmarco/177.txt` contains information about Eddie Murphy starring in Another 48 Hrs., as well as details about the film's action set pieces, social commentary, comedic talent of Eddie Murphy, and diverse cast of supporting characters.\n* The document with file path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_462/re-ranker-msmarco/147.txt` contains information about Eddie Murphy's career, including his roles in various movies, but does not directly mention Another 48 Hrs. as one of them.\n\nBased on this analysis, I conclude that the triple \"Eddie Murphy stars in Another 48 Hrs.\" is supported by the context information provided. Therefore:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents mention that Eddie Murphy starred in \"Another 48 Hrs.,\" which confirms the query statement is correct."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}